<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on CF-Puppeteer</title>
    <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on CF-Puppeteer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>HappyTobi / Tobias Schug</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.0.0-rc.0</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.0.0-rc0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.0.0-rc0/</guid>
      <description>Release 1.0.0-rc.0 - First release candiate
With the first rc we dont bring &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; features!, we just bring the deployment on the newest level of cf api&amp;rsquo;s. The new version now supports the newest structure of cf-manifests.yml files. The plugin is also a &amp;ldquo;complete&amp;rdquo; rewrite of the older versions.
For the new rc versions we will focus on bringing docker support, adding more tests and clean / simplify the plugin implementation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 0.0.14</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.14/</guid>
      <description>Release 0.0.14 brings just small bug fixes and one new feature
Changelog Added  health check settings (v3): fallback on app manifest for health-check-type and health-check-http-endpoint settings print more information on Cloud Foundry API calls (if env CF_PUPPETEER_TRACE = true)  Fixed  health check settings (v3): support for applications with empty command go linting issues  Changed  improve documentation  Specials Special thanks to the first contributor to cf-puppeteer plugin Skyfalke</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 0.0.13</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.13/</guid>
      <description>Release 0.0.13 was a big feature and bugfix release. With the new release we will start with focus to bring the first Verion 1.0.0 to our customers.
With the release we changed following things
Changelog Added  add -vendor-option to stop old service instead of deletion add &amp;ndash;health-check v3 command to specify a invocationtime for health checks  Changed  cleanup manifest parser update documentation  Fixed  env arg issue when passing key value pairs argument handling  Specials Special thanks to the first contributor to cf-puppeteer plugin Skyfalke</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Version 0.0.12</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.12/</guid>
      <description>Release 0.0.12 was a feature and bugfix release.
With the release we changed following things
Changelog Added  add -env argument to pass environment variables  Changed  Change buildscript to generate sha1 sums for each file  Fixed  timeout issue with specified timout at manifest (before -t worked only) documentation  Download: Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Version 0.0.11</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.11/</guid>
      <description>New new release verion of cf-puppeteer was just a rename because a naming confict of cf-plugins Issue
Download: Github</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>