<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CF-Puppeteer: zero-downtime plugin on CF-Puppeteer</title>
    <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CF-Puppeteer: zero-downtime plugin on CF-Puppeteer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>HappyTobi / Tobias Schug</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.1.3</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.3/</guid>
      <description>Release 1.1.3
With the release of cf-puppeteer 1.1.3 we just fixed and improve some small but important things.
Feedback Please give some feedback and open a issues if you find one. github-issue tracker
Changelog Changed 🛠  Improve logging Add error message for manifest path declarative (when the path contains a wildcard)  Fixed 🐛  Venerable application will be deleted correct after pushing a application Typos, error messages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.1.2</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.2/</guid>
      <description>Release 1.1.2
With the release of cf-puppeteer 1.1.2 we worked on backporting some v3 features to the legacy-push option. We also implemented the possibility to use all features with docker images.
All new features and bugfixes are listed below.
New Legacy-push options:
--route-only --no-route  New v3 options:
--docker-image --docker-username  Feedback Please give some feedback and open a issues if you find one. github-issue tracker
Changelog Changed 🛠  refactor environment parsing cleanup code update documentation back port &amp;ldquo;&amp;ndash;no-route&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;&amp;ndash;route-only&amp;rdquo; option to &amp;ldquo;&amp;ndash;legacy-push&amp;rdquo; (v2).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.1.1</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.1/</guid>
      <description>Release 1.1.1
With the release of cf-puppeteer 1.1.1 we worked on some feedback of the community and make the usability easier and more user friendly
All new features and bugfixes are listed below.
--no-route --venerable-action  Examples No-routes Deploy the application without route switching - old application should still run and new one should be stoped after deployment. (Venerable-action will be set to none automatically )
cf zero-downtime-push -f .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release 1.1.0
With the release of cf-puppeteer version 1.1.0 we bring some new features and bugfixes.
The new features and bugfixes are listed below.
--no-route --route-only  Examples No-routes Deploy the application without route switching - old application should still run and new one should be stoped after deployment
cf zero-downtime-push -f ./manifest.yml --no-route --vendor-option none  right now you can add new services or what ever you want. To start the new application with routes and cleanup the old one you can do the following things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.0.0</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release 1.0.0 - Final release is here
With the first final release we bring the version 1.0.0 to cf-puppeteer. We bring some small features, many bug fixes and a complete refactoring of the old version of cf-puppeterr.
Right now it&amp;rsquo;s possible to choose between an v2 or v3 cf push of your application. CF-Puppeteer checks the cf-controller version and use the v3 push if it&amp;rsquo;s possible. To use the old push manually you can pass the option: --legacy-push</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.0.0-rc.0</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.0.0-rc0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_1.0.0-rc0/</guid>
      <description>Release 1.0.0-rc.0 - First release candiate
With the first rc we dont bring &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; features!, we just pushed the deployment on the newest level of cf api&amp;rsquo;s. The new version now supports the newest structure of cf-manifests.yml files. The plugin is also a &amp;ldquo;complete&amp;rdquo; rewrite of the older versions.
For the new rc versions we will focus on bringing docker support, adding more tests and clean / simplify the plugin implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 0.0.14</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.14/</guid>
      <description>Release 0.0.14 brings just small bug fixes and one new feature
Changelog Added  health check settings (v3): fallback on app manifest for health-check-type and health-check-http-endpoint settings print more information on Cloud Foundry API calls (if env CF_PUPPETEER_TRACE = true)  Fixed  health check settings (v3): support for applications with empty command go linting issues  Changed  improve documentation  Specials Special thanks to the first contributor to cf-puppeteer plugin Skyfalke</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Version 0.0.13</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.13/</guid>
      <description>Release 0.0.13 was a big feature and bugfix release. With the new release we will start with focus to bring the first Verion 1.0.0 to our customers.
With the release we changed following things
Changelog Added  add -vendor-option to stop old service instead of deletion add &amp;ndash;health-check v3 command to specify a invocationtime for health checks  Changed  cleanup manifest parser update documentation  Fixed  env arg issue when passing key value pairs argument handling  Specials Special thanks to the first contributor to cf-puppeteer plugin Skyfalke</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Version 0.0.12</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.12/</guid>
      <description>Release 0.0.12 was a feature and bugfix release.
With the release we changed following things
Changelog Added  add -env argument to pass environment variables  Changed  Change buildscript to generate sha1 sums for each file  Fixed  timeout issue with specified timout at manifest (before -t worked only) documentation  Download: Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Version 0.0.11</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/posts/release_0.0.11/</guid>
      <description>New new release verion of cf-puppeteer was just a rename because a naming confict of cf-plugins Issue
Download: Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licenses</title>
      <link>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cf-puppeteer.happytobi.com/licenses/</guid>
      <description>Images here you can find all used images from the website - Unsplash - Puppeteer - pixpoetry - Unsplash - Release 0.0.11 - Ankush Minda - Unsplash - Release 0.0.12 - Daniel Hjalmarsson - Unsplash - Release 0.0.13 - Glenn Carstens-Peters - Unsplash - Release 1.0.0 - Pietro Rampazzo - Unsplash - Release 1.1.0 - Samuel Zeller - Unsplash - Release 1.1.1 - eberhard grossgasteiger - Unsplash - Release 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>